let questions =[
  {
      numb: 1,
      question: "What is my D.O.B ?",
      answer: "23rd Nov 2002",
      options:[
          "17th Nov 2002",
          "23rd Nov 2003",
          "23rd Nov 2002",
          "17th Nov 2001"
      ]
  },
  {
      numb: 2,
      question: "Where is my Home town ?",
      answer: "Sabroom",
      options:[
          "Santir Bazar",
          "Belonia",
          "Sabroom",
          "Amarpur"
      ]
  },
  {
      numb: 3,
      question: "What is my Age ?",
      answer: "21",
      options:[
          "21",
          "19",
          "20",
          "22"
      ]
  },
  {
      numb: 4,
      question: "What is Ssnkr's anytime film to watch ?",
      answer: "Yeh Jawani Hai Dewaani",
      options:[
          "Adipurush",
          "KGF",
          "DDLJ",
          "Yeh Jawani Hai Dewaani"
      ]
  },
  {
      numb: 5,
      question: "Where Ssnkr recently went for trekking ?",
      answer: "Uttrakhand",
      options:[
          "Nepal",
          "Uttrakhand",
          "Delhi",
          "Arunachal Pradesh"
      ]
  },
  {
      numb: 6,
      question: "What is Ssnkr's height ?",
      answer: "Ssnkr also don't know!",
      options:[
          "172 cm",
          "175 cm",
          "169 cm",
          "Ssnkr also don't know!"
      ]
  },
  {
      numb: 7,
      question: "If not Engg. what would Ssnkr be ?",
      answer: "Owner of Counter",
      options:[
          "Army",
          "Doctor",
          "Owner of Counter",
          "Cricketer"
      ]
  },
  {
      numb: 8,
      question: "What is Ssnkr's nickname ?",
      answer: "All of the above",
      options:[
          "Penthu",
          "Susu",
          "Emon",
          "All of the above"
      ]
  },
  {
      numb: 9,
      question: "What Snnkr do in free time ?",
      answer: "Watch movies",
      options:[
          "Watch movies",
          "Sleep",
          "Video Games",
          "Preapre for GATE"
      ]
  },
  {
      numb: 10,
      question: "Favourite cricketer ?",
      answer: "Virat Kohli",
      options:[
          "Gautam Gambhir",
          "Virat Kohli",
          "MS Dhoni",
          "BKL Rahul"
      ]
  },
]